原视频名：“Blue Skies Went to Black:” Mission Recap: Launch Demo 2 | Virgin Orbit
原作者名： Virgin Orbit
视频来源：youtu.be/yrx2PBzeRdU
原视频发布日期：20210118
字幕翻译/压制：旋火
[Music]
[音乐]
LC全称可能是Launch Complex, LD是Launch Director
LC, this is LD on Control Room.
发射场 我是控制室的指令长
We are currently on track for our nominal timeline,
目前 我们正按原定时间表进行
and our current drop time as listed in Trillian is 19:25 UTC.
而我们目前的空投时间如Trillian中所列出的 是UTC时间19点25分
Plane on Control Room. Flight Crew has been boarded on the aircraft.
飞机在控制室 机组人员已登上飞机
Cosmic Girl, this is Orbit Base.
宇宙女孩 这里是(维珍)轨道基地
You are go for takeoff.
你们可以起飞了
Copy, go for takeoff.
收到 准备起飞
Altitude 3,000.
高度3000
And Orbit Base, Cosmic Girl is starting the turn to the inbound.
轨道基地 宇宙女孩开始转弯向内
Pulling now.
现在开始拉起
Pull.
拉起
Pulling.
正在拉起
Release.
释放
Release, release, release
释放 释放 释放
PST is ignited.
PST(?)已点火
Confirmed, NewtonThree engine startup
牛顿3发动机启动确认
Max Alpha achieved.
达到最大攻角
TVCs and first stage looking good
矢量推进系统与一级正常
We have a pretty awesome view up here
我们这里的风景很不错
Max Q Alpha achieved.
达到最大气动压力
Stage One burn nominal.
一级发动机点火正常
Stage Sep. Breakwires broken.
一二级分离 分离线缆断开
NewtonFour startup complete.
牛顿4发动机完成启动
[Cosmic Girl] has recovered, and we are now returning to base.
[宇宙女孩]已经改出 我们正在返回基地
Fairing breakwires broken.
整流罩分离线缆断开
LauncherOne's in space.
LauncherOne已进入太空
穿过大气层进入太空后，天空的颜色会变黑
"Sounds like the blue skies went to black!"
看来蓝天已经变黑了
(Joyous laughter)
（欢乐的笑声）
This is Radiohead on control.
这里是控制中心的无线电
Mauritius has confirmed acquisition signal.
毛里求斯遥测信号正常
Payload separation confirmed.
有效载荷分离确认
(Cheers and celebratory jubilee)
(欢呼声和庆祝)